fashionfantasygame.com 2018-05-14

# Fashion Fantasy Game - Privacy Policy

R. Lilly Tuckerwear Inc. Privacy Policy 

The "www.fashionfantasygame.com" website is owned and operated by R. Lilly Tuckerwear Inc. ("we" or "us"). Your privacy is important to us at R. Lilly Tuckerwear Inc. Therefore, we encourage you to read this policy to find out: 

  1. What personally identifiable information may be collected through this website. 
  2. How we may use the information.
  3. With whom the information may be shared.
  4. What choices are available to you and your parents regarding our collection and use of the information.
  5. How you or your parent can correct any inaccuracies in the information or request that we delete it from our database.
  6. What kind of security procedures we have in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control.
  7. Notice of updates to our privacy policy.
  8. Other information.

SPECIAL NOTE TO KIDS: 

If you are under 13 years old, you should ask your parent or guardian BEFORE giving out any information about yourself, such as your name, age, address or e-mail address. We do not ask you to reveal any information that will identify you except your email address, your date of birth and your first name when you register to play the Fashion Fantasy Game. Remember, if you are under 13, you must have your parent or guardian make any changes to personal information given to us in the past. If you are ever unsure about anything you are seeing on this Web site, ask your parent or guardian for help. Players under 13 will have limited access to certain game features until consent is provided. 

If you are under 13, we may knowingly collect your email address, which is personally identifiable information, we also ask for non-personally identifiable information such as first name and date of birth. ONE OF OUR RULES IS THAT YOU CREATE A SCREEN NAME WHICH DOES NOT INCLUDE ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION. 

INFORMATION FOR PARENTS OF KIDS UNDER 13: 

We collect information from our players at the time of registration and in the event that they are subscribing to paid services or making a purchase. If a visitor indicates that he/she is under the age of 13, he/she will be asked to supply a parent's or guardian's email address. Players accounts registered to visitors under 13 are given restricted access to certain features of FashionFantasyGame.com. When a parental email is provided, we notify parents of the information collected from their child and provide a link to our privacy policies. Additionally, before allowing a player who has registered as under 13 years old, access to enhanced game features, parents must provide affirmative consent to the kid's participation in community features. If the parent responds by completing a consent form and submitting it by fax or regular mail, we then follow that communication with an e-mail confirmation to the parent and allow the kid to participate with enhanced access to the game. Although the child is permitted to play before parental consent is provided, they are only given access to a limited set of site features until we receive parental consent or until the player turns 13 years old. We also retain the parent's email address in case we need to notify the parent of any policy or other changes and to enable the parent to review, change and delete their child’s personal information collected in our records. When players under 13 do not provide a parent’s email address or the supplied email address is invalid, email addresses collected from players will be revised and stored in our database in a non-retrievable format until we are contacted by the player and provided with a functional parental email address.   
We only ask for and collect information from players, personally identifiable information that is reasonably necessary for them to participate in any given activity online. We also may collect this information to respond to a specific request from a kid under 13. If parents have removed their child’s personal information from our database, once we respond to a request from a child under 13, we may not contact that player again and the information is deleted from our records. We take very seriously the safety of kids, especially those under 13 and may also collect this information to protect that safety. If we do collect additional information to protect the safety of your child, we provide notice to you and we do not use that information for any other purpose. You can always ask us to review or delete any of your child's information and you can refuse to permit further collection or use of your child's information at any time by following the procedures described in Parent Portal. However, if you ask us to delete your child's information that is necessary to participate in our activities, we may have to ask your child not to participate in our activities. 

We urge parents to explore the Fashion Fantasy Game and our site with their children and closely monitor their children's online activities. 

Please also read the rest of our privacy policy. 

1\. Information We Collect 

We do not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you register, upgrade your account, make a purchase or actively sign up for a newsletter or another activity. At this time, we only collect your email address, first name and date of birth and gender when you register to play the Fashion Fantasy Game. If players register as under 13, we request also request a parent’s email address. With respect to our visitors under 13, we do not collect more personally identifiable information than reasonably necessary to enable them to participate in a particular activity, and we request parental consent to have full featured access to FashionFantasyGame.com. The parental request form will ask for a parent’s full name, phone number and a signature. See INFORMATION FOR PARENTS OF KIDS UNDER 13. 

For other activities, such as where users request to be an R. Lilly Style Girl or where they can submit content (e.g., fashion ideas, pictures of their favorite styles, contests), we may ask users to submit information about their interests and preferences (e.g., favorite styles and fashion ideas). Visitors who order merchandise from our Site will be required to provide their full name, billing and mailing addresses, e-mail address, telephone number and a credit card number or other payment processing information. Where an order is being shipped to a third party, we also will need the recipient's name and mailing address. On occasion, we may request additional information regarding a shopper's preferences. 

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information, such as the type of computer operating system you are using (e.g., Windows or Mac OS), the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the domain name of the Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink), or information about the pages you viewed or activities in which you participated. The intention is to provide the user with a better on line experience. Also see Use of Cookies and Other Technologies. 

Invite-A-Friend   
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your email address and your friend's email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. We do not store this information after sending this email.   
Just to verify,   
The email address that the friend sees—should be the RLilly site and not the senders email address. I think you can ask for first name as well if you want.   
There should be no space where kids can freely type in a message (for under 13’s without consent). 

2\. How We Use Information 

We use personally identifiable information collected at our site to respond to visitors' requests for information and customer support, enable registered players to participate in the Fashion Fantasy Game and other site activities, serve prizes to our contest or sweepstakes winners, or provide our newsletter or other information about the Fashion Fantasy Game or events to our players. We also may use personally identifiable information provided by shoppers or by parents or adults in other sections of our site to send them, by e-mail or direct mail, notification of special offers or events. 

Your screen name is displayed throughout the Fashion Fantasy Game website to facilitate interaction in the game and it is used if you communicate with other players. Also, we may publish your screen name if you win a contest or a sweepstakes. Participation in the game will enable visitors to design their own clothes or run and style their own stores and if they are 13 years old or older or have been given consent by their parent or guardian, enable them to participate in unmonitored chats about fashion, and exchange other information as the player sees fit, but the game will not request any other information. Please be aware that the R. Lilly Rules prohibit players from voluntarily posting personally identifiable information to internal mail boxes or any other public forums in the game, and prohibits the posting of any information that can be accessed by other players and can, in turn, be used by those persons to send unsolicited communications. See R. Lilly Rules. 

We use parents' e-mail addresses to notify them when we have received personally identifiable information, such as e-mail addresses, from their children, and to provide them with the ability to consent to, or opt their children out of, participation in a particular activity. See also INFORMATION FOR PARENTS OF KIDS UNDER 13. 

We may use non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our Web pages, for technical support and to improve our visitors' experience. We also may aggregate this information to analyze site usage, as well as to offer products or services. 

3\. Information Sharing 

We do not share our visitors' personally identifiable information with unrelated third parties for their own marketing or any other purposes without appropriate consent. 

Sometimes, we may need to share personally identifiable information collected at the site with our agents or contractors who, for example, help us conduct a sweepstakes, fulfill customer orders, or assist with customer service. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose 

In addition, we may disclose personally identifiable information to third parties to respond to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, detect, prevent, or take action against illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, enforce our terms of service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Site and applicable laws, or as otherwise required or permitted by law or consistent with legal requirements. 

Authorize.Net and PayPal: We use credit card and payment processing companies to bill you for goods and services. 

We may transfer personally identifiable information collected at the site if we are acquired by, sold to, or merged with another company. 

We share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners and advertisers. This information does not identify individual users. We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information. 

4\. Your/Your Parent's Choices 

See INFORMATION FOR PARENTS OF KIDS UNDER 13. If you are under 13, your parent or guardian may at any time change or delete the information we have about you. See Parent Portal. 

We provide you the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, when you register for the service, but do not wish to receive any newsletters from us you can indicate your preference on your registration form. 

If you no longer wish to receive our promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication or by emailing us at info@rlillytuckerwear.com. 

You will be notified if your personal information will be collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party 

5\. Your/Your Parent's Changes 

This Web site gives users options for changing and modifying information previously provided. If you are a registered visitor, you are welcome to view, change or delete your registration information at any time, or to update the contact information we have for you or to inform us that you do not want to receive new product or other information from us. Simply go to the Parent Portal on this Web site and follow the directions. 

Kids under 13 cannot change registration information. Only their parent or guardian can do that. If you wish to review, correct or delete information that we may have about you or your child, or wish to inform us that you do not permit further collection or use of your child's information, please contact us at the following address: 

Fashion Fantasy Game, R Lilly Tuckerwear, 120 East End Avenue, New York, NY 10028; info@rlillytuckerwear.com. 

Or go to the Parent Portal. 

6\. Security 

We have implemented safeguards to maintain data security and correctly use the information we collect online. The hosting site sits behind a Cisco PIX Firewall. The database is protected with username/password and firewall rules for access. Because we are sensitive to visitors' security concerns about the use of credit cards to purchase products over the Internet, for online orders we use a technology that encrypts credit card data while information is being transmitted over the Internet, provided that the visitor's browser supports the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. 

7\. Updates to Our Policy 

From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy. We will notify you about any material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by placing a notice on our Site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this Privacy Policy. 

We will also provide parents notice by e-mail of any material changes in the way we intend to collect, use, and/or share kids' personal information. Please note that, at all times, parents should update their personal information to provide us current e-mail addresses. 

8\. Other Information 

Use of Cookies and Other Technologies 

To enhance your experience when you visit our site, we send one or more "cookies." Cookies are small text files that we place in visitors' computer browsers to store their preferences. We may use cookies to determine how many visitors we have and how often they visit various sections of our Site. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can adjust your browser to reject all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Please note that certain areas of our site can only be accessed in conjunction with cookies and if you disable them, you may not be able to access some of our content. 

Links to Other Sites 

Our Site may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. You should consult the other sites' privacy policies, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. 

Questions and Suggestions 

If you have questions or suggestions about this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at: 

info@rlillytuckerwear.com, or Nancy Ganz, R. Lilly Tuckerwear, 120 East End Ave, 9b, New York. NY 10028
